Uh, good night for the Packers. Uh, you
know, excited to add the players that we
did and I'm sure you guys get some
questions. So, shoot.
>> Brian, it's obviously tough having a
draft out of the first round pick. Is
you drawn up a too many better? These
are probably what you
>> Yeah, you know, the board held up good.
Um, you know, there's always guys that,
you know, like we talked about yesterday
that that go that you're kind of, you
know, disappointed that they went like
in every draft. Um but yeah, no, I mean,
you know, um you know, we really had,
you know, a few players with that first
pick at 52 um that we liked and it was
kind of a tough tough decision there. Um
and then um a couple of them hung around
and we went and tried to get one and we
did. So um was excited to kind of come
out of that and there's still a lot of
good players left on the board and um
you know, we we we took some cracks
maybe getting back into the bottom of
the third round. Didn't happen, but um
you know, we're excited for tomorrow as
well. you were thinking Chris at 52 as
well.
>> Yeah, we we we we thought he's that kind
of player, you know. So, um again um we
had a number of players uh um at that
pick that we really we liked with it.
Was it was a little bit more than I
would have expected. So, um like I said,
the board held up good and um yeah, so
we'll see how it goes tomorrow.
>> What did you what did you like about
Mlen over some of the other detackles
like you you don't have to like bag any
other guys, but Orange was out there and
Florida State guy. Yeah, I mean I think
obviously, you know, he played in the
SEC. Uh he's a huge man. Uh has
excellent length. Um and I think that
for me the combination of being able to
play the nose, the the three and and and
actually rush the passer. There's a lot
of these guys that that don't do that.
Um he can. And then that was I think
what set him apart a little bit for us.
>> What was it that with Brandon?
>> Yeah. You know, he's a he's a he's one
of those guys. He's one of the few guys
that can play off man, can play press.
Uh his suddenness through transition is
something that, you know, stood out to
us. He's very young. We think his best
football is ahead of him. We think he's
got so much more left uh in the tank. Um
not only um as a player, but physically
as well. We think he'll get bigger and
stronger. So, um again, um you know, he
was again one of those players that um
um didn't see being available when we
were picking at 52. We were sure happy
that he did. really like the fact that
he took the step and went to South
Carolina last year and kind of, you
know, better competition and and really
showed well this past year.
>> Was there any was there any hesitation,
Brian, in taking a corner that's only 20
years old or is that almost more
attractive because you see the you know
>> Yeah. Um yeah. No, not really. I mean,
you know, obviously we investigate those
things and we work through, but I think
we do think, again, we've always tried
to take guys that we think that have
more left, you know, in development and,
um, uh, he played at a high level this
year. We think he's going to be able to
help us next year and we think his
upside is really good. So, no, I mean, I
think, uh, you know, there's there's not
a lot of 20-year-olds in the draft. Um,
we took one one time in Kenny Clark,
that worked out pretty well. So, um, you
know, hopefully this works out that
well, but uh, no, it was no hesitation.
So Brian, if you were considering trying
to get back in the third, would it cost
you some more picks tomorrow? As it
stands, you only have five tomorrow,
which seven total will be your fewest.
Do you feel like you're at a position
with this team where it's just about the
quality of guy rather than just swings
at the plate like you've done before?
>> Yeah. Um I always like as many swings at
the plate as we can get. Um but uh I do
I do like our team. I like our depth. I
like our roster. Um, so, you know, I do
think that, uh, we got a tough team to
make. Um, but, um, you know, again, I,
you know, I think the more swings at the
plate, the better. You know, I really
do. Um, but, uh, I do feel, um, if the,
if the quality of the player that's up
on that board is worth it, then it's
willing to kind of to to do some of
that.
>> These are, uh, two positions where you
could really use the help in 2026.
Um, do you think it's realistic to think
that these two guys can get on the field
and and help you this year?
>> I do. I mean, obviously we got to get
them here and we got to, you know, get
around our culture, around our team, our
environment. Um, but obviously we
wouldn't have taken them aside if we
didn't think they could help us right
away. Um, but um, like all these
players, every one of them that got
picked today and and yesterday and the
guys that'll be picked tomorrow, uh,
their NFL journey is just starting and
it's a whole different world and it's
going to take them a little bit of time
to to adapt. Um, but I think both these
guys um have shown they they both are
transfer guys and they both adapted to
their new situations fairly quickly, you
know. So, um, you know, I feel pretty
confident that they could help us, you
know, sooner rather than later.
>> Has that become a piece of the evaluate?
You know, we talked about NIL and
transfer. Has that become a new piece of
the evaluation is how guys transition
from one school to another?
>> 100%. I think uh you know I think so
many of these guys have done that now
and um you know I think um the reason
why they transferred is important to us
and then how how they adjusted to that
new surrounding and how quickly they
could do it and um you know so you know
again we're we're talking to people at
every school that they've been at trying
to find out about these guys but I do
think uh the reasons why they
transferred um and then you know how
that transition went is important for us
to know
>> the good reason? What's the bad reason
for a transfer in your mind?
>> Well, some transfers because they're not
allowed back. So, you know, um but uh
no, uh I just think, you know, some of
these guys are if they're looking for
improvement, you know, if they're
looking for better competition, um I
think those are the things that, uh make
some sense to us that because it's that
important to them to be the best that
they can be. even though, you know, kind
of going to another school in a
different conference that might be
tougher on them might not work out for
them, but they had the they had the guts
to do it, you know. So, I think that's a
good reason for some of these guys to do
that. Um, you know, sometimes it's
strictly financial now, you know, and um
not that that's a bad reason, but it's
different. Um, but I think um, you know,
we're investigating all that to kind of
see see why.
>> Why was it important to extend Jaden
Reed and and how much of a priority is
is getting Watson locked up? Yeah. Um,
first question, um, because he helps us
win, man. He's he's one of those guys.
He's a winning football player. Um, you
know, obviously missed some time last
year, but when he's on the field, we're
a better football team, you know, and
there's no doubt about it. We're really
excited to get that done. Uh, I don't
know if we've done many many of those
contracts during the draft, you know,
but um, I'm glad we did. Uh, and
absolutely with Christian and another
amongst a bunch of other guys that we're
going to hope over the next few months
to try to maybe do some some of that
with. So, um, you know, excited for him,
uh, and his family, um, but more excited
about our team and what what he can
bring to it moving forward.
>> Ryan, there are times when you had your
pref press conference where I'm not sure
how much is a full truth is always being
shared, but you told us
>> you guys lie to me.
>> No, just, you know, the exchange,
>> but you told us point blank you wanted
to add bodies at corner. You had an
appetite for a nose tackle
>> and that's what you did. Did you kind of
enter today with a feeling like you were
in a good position to do that or is it
just how the values and the needs lined
up? What do you see there? What was your
sense?
>> Yeah, I I thought the board was pretty
strong at defensive tackle. Um corner
maybe not as much. Um but uh so you
never know how that's going to shake
out. It's really kind of when those runs
happen. We weren't high enough in the
second round to kind of like say, "Okay,
we're going to be in involved in that no
matter what." Um, so if we were going to
try to, you know, guarantee something,
we were going to have to jump up. And,
um, we we looked at some of the stuff,
didn't make sense, you know. Um, but,
uh, um, you know, when it when it came
down to it, um, you know, like I said,
we had we had multiple choices and, uh,
Brandon was just, it was for sure the
right move there.
>> What do you think of McCoyy's ball? And
what do you what do you see there?
>> Who who's that?
>> McCoy the corner.
>> Oh, Jamad.
>> Yeah. Um, yeah, I think he's working
through some things. I'm not exactly
sure why. Um, but there's obviously
obviously a lot of things that are in
play there.
>> You guys had a real medical concern
there.
>> Um, I'm not going to talk I'm not going
to talk about these guys medical stuff.
Pete, you know that?
>> Ryan, was your intel just kind of
telling you that Mlullen might not get
to 84? Is that why you had to jump?
>> Yeah, I mean, I wouldn't say there was
anything specific intelwise. I just felt
like um you know from the soon as we
made the pick at 52 I was I was
interested in seeing where we could get
to what might make sense to give us a
chance to get him. Um and there was a
few other guys on the board as well and
um you know um it just it worked out
that way. It wasn't anything there
wasn't like I didn't have a specific
this he's going to get taken. I just
felt that it was important for us to try
to acquire him. And as we as the as the
uh third round kind of, you know, ca
came kept going, um he was he was kind
of that one guy sticking up there.
>> What what do you want to get out of
tomorrow?
>> Yeah, I think um again, um you wouldn't
mind moving around a little bit. Um I
think like I said, I think I think the
board's strong. I think there's good
players up there. Um, and just really
kind of, you know, we it's always hard
just to stick to the very best player
available, but particularly on on the
third day. I think if you can do that,
uh, you're you're better off. And so,
um, you know, I don't I don't feel a
pressing need. I didn't feel that coming
into this draft and I don't feel that
now that we have to go, you know, just
fill a spot. Um, so hopefully I can have
the discipline to to kind of just stay
there and take the best player and and
and do that. Five five defensive tackles
were picked tonight uh before you moved
up to 77, but that didn't play much of a
role in your decision to move up to 77.
>> Uh like I said, I think as the the third
round wore on, he was kind of sticking
out there like a sore thumb. You know
what I mean? Like he was like, "All
right, that's the highest guy and let's,
you know, um let's go get him." You
know, I think that was it. So, um to
some degree, yes. Okay.
>> Mil Mil said something to the effect of
that he'll sleep pretty well tonight
with these two guys that you got today.
Just
>> how do you feel? How will you sleep
tonight?
>> Yeah, I sleep well all the time. So, um
but um No, yeah, I'm I'm really excited
about these two guys. I think they can
help our football team. They I think
they have really bright futures ahead of
them. They were really good players in
college, good teammates. I think they're
going to fit here very very well. And um
you know, I think they're going to you
know, again, I think I have a lot of
faith in our coaches and and our process
here with everybody in this building.
And I think these two guys are wired
right for that. And um so yeah, it's um
you like I said, we got we got more work
to do tomorrow. I'm excited about it. Um
so, but this was a good good first day
for us since we didn't have yesterday.
How challenging how challenging was it
in hindsight to wait and watch 51 picks
go off the board or because of how the
board held up? Was it maybe not as
challenging as you expected it to be?
>> Yeah, like like Ryan, like I like I said
this, it's always hard watching these
guys come off. And I think uh you know I
think time and experience gives me you
know an understanding that these guys
are going to come off. I think when I
was younger, you you know, you'd focus
in on a couple guys thinking, "Oh, maybe
there's a chance," you know, and uh um I
think time and experience is kind of
exhausted. That's I don't I don't look
at it that way anymore. It's more um I'm
into numbers and and and trying to see
where the board is strong and where we
need to be and um what's going to help
the Packers the most. But um it's always
it's always hard watching really good
players get taken, particularly, you
know, by teams you don't want them to go
to.
How much were you thinking about um
Ganon's defense and how these guys would
fit when when you took them? Are they
scheme specific?
>> Yeah, Tom, I don't ever really think too
much about that. Whether it's Jeff
Hafley or Jonathan Ganon, I'm trying to
find the best well-rounded football
players that can do everything that
they're going to be asked to do because
I think when you start getting too
scheme specific, as soon as you have
injuries, you could be in in bad shape,
right? because it's all of a sudden now
he's he's not he's got to do something
different because he's he's um he's a
backup player and and the guy that got
hurt isn't isn't what he does well. So
um but I do think you know with what
Jonathan's going to do you know I
thought you know certainly adding big
people was going to be important for us
because I think we're going to need a
little bit more of them. Um, but in
general, I've never um I've never tried
to allow the scheme thing too much into
it because um you know, you're you're in
game six and you got a bunch of guys
playing out of position because you have
to because injuries and if they're not
wellrounded enough, you're you could be
in pretty bad shape.
>> Back to Matt's question about Jaden. Um
you just paid him. You've got a bunch of
big contracts. You got Tucker coming up.
Can you afford to do Watson as well? Is
there enough?
>> Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. No, obviously
this is something, you know, it's it's a
little bit of long-term planning. Russ
and I spend a lot of time on this and
and um you know, again, we we let a lot
of really good players, you know, walk
out of here this this past offseason,
but with the thought process of there's
some guys that we really we want to lock
up. So, that'll be the intention. We'll
see kind of where it goes, but yeah, I
don't I don't foresee anything being a
problem.
>> Brian, I'm guessing you don't go into
the draft saying, "I want to have eight
picks. I want to have 12 picks." I know
you want as many swings.
>> Y,
>> but like you've had a year where you had
13. and you got a ton of picks next
year. So, do you want to add at least a
couple of picks tomorrow or if you end
up with a seven player class? Yeah,
>> you're fine with it.
>> Yeah, I I'll be fine with it. Uh Jason,
but at the same time, like, you know, um
depending on how tomorrow falls, um if
the board's going to be stronger, you
know, maybe moving down a little bit and
adding some picks, whether that's this
year, whether that's next year, uh I'm
kind of all for that. Um but, um you
know, I think we sitting in a pretty
good spot right now. uh not only this
year but next year. Um so um I'm not
gonna I don't think I'll you know unless
the board looks a certain way I don't
think I'll I'll pass up picking a player
that I want to pick just to add picks. I
don't think it's that that kind of draft
for us.